# data.py
COLOURS = [
    {"prompt": "Blue", "answer": "Bleu"},
    {"prompt": "Green", "answer": "Vert"},
    {"prompt": "Yellow", "answer": "Jaune"},
    {"prompt": "Red", "answer": "Rouge"},
    {"prompt": "White", "answer": "Blanc"},
    {"prompt": "Black", "answer": "Noir"},
    {"prompt": "Pink", "answer": "Rose"},
    {"prompt": "Grey", "answer": "Gris"},
    {"prompt": "Orange", "answer": "Orange"},
    {"prompt": "Brown", "answer": "Marron"},
]

FRUITS = [
    {"prompt": "Apple", "answer": "Pomme"},
    {"prompt": "Banana", "answer": "Banane"},
    {"prompt": "Strawberry", "answer": "Fraise"},
    {"prompt": "Grape", "answer": "Raisin"},
    {"prompt": "Pear", "answer": "Poire"},
    {"prompt": "Peach", "answer": "Pêche"},
    {"prompt": "Cherry", "answer": "Cerise"},
    {"prompt": "Pineapple", "answer": "Ananas"},
    {"prompt": "Lemon", "answer": "Citron"},
    {"prompt": "Watermelon", "answer": "Pastèque"},
]
